<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<component type="desktop">
  <!--Created with jdAppdataEdit 4.2-->
  <id>info.cemu.Cemu</id>
  <name>Cemu</name>
  <summary>Nintendo Wii U Emulator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Nintendo Wii U Emulator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Émulateur Nintendo Wii U</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Nintendo Wii U Emulator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Εξομοιωτής Nintendo Wii U</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Emulador de Nintendo Wii U</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Emulador Nintendo Wii U</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Emulatore Nintendo Wii U</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Nintendo Wii U Emulaattori</summary>
  <developer_name>Cemu Project</developer_name>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">info.cemu.Cemu.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MPL-2.0</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>Cemu is a Nintendo Wii U emulator that is able to run most Wii U games and homebrew in a playable state. Created by Exzap, and written in C/C++.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Cemu ist ein Nintendo Wii U-Emulator, der die meisten Wii U Spiele und Homebrew in einem spielbaren Zustand ausführen kann. Erstellt von Exzap, und geschrieben in C/C++.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Cemu est un émulateur de Wii U capable de lancer la plupart des jeux Wii U et des homebrews en interface de jeu. Crée par Exzap, et développé en C/C++.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Cemu is een Nintendo Wii U emulator die de meeste Wii U en Homebrew games speelbaar kan runnen. Het project is begonnen door Exzap, en het is geschreven in C/C++.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Cemu είναι ένας προσομοιωτής της κονσόλας Nintendo Wii U που προσομοιώνει επίσημα παιχνίδια, καθώς και μη επίσημα προγράμματα ("homebrew") του Wii U. Δημιουργήθηκε από τον Exzap σε C/C++.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Cemu es un emulador de Nintendo Wii U que es capaz de ejecutar la mayoría de los juegos de Wii U y homebrew en un estado jugable. Creado por Exzap, y escrito en C y C++.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Cemu é um emulador de Nintendo Wii U que é capaz de executar a maioría dos jogos de Wii U e homebrew em um estado jogavel. Criado por Exzap, e escrito em C e C++.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Cemu è un emulatore del Nintendo Wii U in grado di eseguire in stato giocabile la maggior parte dei giochi e homebrew per Wii U. Creato da Exzap, e scritto in C/C++.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Cemu on Wii U -emulaattori, joka pystyy toistamaan useimpia Wii U -pelejä ja homebrew'ta pelikelvollisesti. Luonut Exzap, kirjoitettu C:llä/C++:lla.</p>    
    <p>This emulator aims at providing both high-accuracy and performance, and is actively being developed with new features and fixes to increase compatibility, convenience and usability.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Dieser Emulator zielt darauf ab, sowohl hohe Genauigkeit als auch Leistung zu bieten, und wird aktiv mit neuen Funktionen und Korrekturen weiterentwickelt, um Kompatibilität, Komfort und Benutzerfreundlichkeit zu verbessern.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Cet émulateur vise à la fois à offrir fidélité et performance, il est activement développé avec des nouvelles fonctionnalités et des correctifs pour augmenter la compatibilité, la commodité et la facilité d'utilisation.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">De emulator richt zich op integriteit en snelheid, en wordt continu verder ontwikkeld met nieuwe toevoegingen en fixes om de compatibiliteit, het gemak en de gebruiksvriendelijkheid te verbeteren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Ο προσομοιωτής αυτός στοχεύει τόσο στην ακρίβεια, όσο και στην ταχύτητα, και βελτιώνεται συνεχώς με νέες δυνατότητες και διορθώσεις που τον καθιστούν πιο βολικό, εύκολο στην χρήση και συμβατό με περισσότερα παιχνίδια.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Este emulador tiene como objetivo proporcionar tanto alta precisión como rendimiento y se desarrolla activamente con nuevas características y correcciones para mejorar la compatibilidad, la comodidad y la usabilidad.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Esse emulador visa proporcionar tanto alta precisão como rendimento e está sendo ativamente desenvolvido com novas características e correções para melhorar a compatibilidade, a comodidade e a usabilidade.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Questo emulatore ha l'obiettivo di fornire sia alta precisione che alte prestazioni, ed è in continuo sviluppo con nuove funzionalità e correzioni per aumentare la compatibilità, la comodità e l'usabilità.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tämä emulaattori pyrkii tarjoamaan korkeaa tarkkuutta sekä suorituskykyä, ja sitä kehitetään aktiivisesti uusilla ominaisuuksilla ja korjauksilla, jotka parantavat yhteensopivuutta, mukavuutta ja käytettävyyttä..</p>
    <p>It was written from scratch and development on the project began roughly early 2015.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Er wird seit Anfang 2015 entwickelt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Il a été écrit à partir de zéro et son développement a débuté vers le début de l'année 2015.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Ontwikkeling van Cemu begon ongeveer in het voorjaar van 2015.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Αρχισε απο το τίποτα και βρίσκεται υπό ανάπτυξη από το 2015.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Fue escrito desde cero y el desarrollo del proyecto comenzó aproximadamente a principios de 2015.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Foi escrito do zero e o desenvolvimento do projeto começou aproximadamente a princípio de 2015.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">È stato scritto da zero e lo sviluppo del progetto è cominciato intorno all'inizio del 2015.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Se kirjoitettiin tyhjästä ja sen kehitys alkoi suunnilleen vuoden 2015 alussa.</p>
    
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/58/Cemu_Screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="2.0" date="2022-08-22" type="stable">
      <url>https://github.com/cemu-project/Cemu/releases/tag/v2.0</url>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <url type="homepage">https://cemu.info</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/cemu-project/Cemu/issues</url>
  <url type="faq">https://cemu.info/faq.html</url>
  <url type="help">https://wiki.cemu.info</url>
  <!-- <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/cemu-project/Cemu</url> -->
  <categories>
    <category>Game</category>
    <category>Emulator</category>
  </categories>
  <recommends>
    <memory>8192</memory>
  </recommends>
  <supports>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>gamepad</control>
  </supports>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <provides>
    <binary>cemu</binary>
    <mediatype>application/x-wii-u-rom</mediatype>
  </provides>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>nintendo</keyword>
  </keywords>
</component>
